[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "-NONE-", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Howard Stern, how much of his private parts did he show?", "question_tokens": ["Howard", "Stern", ",", "how", "much", "of", "his", "private", "parts", "did", "he", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "You've got that (INAUDIBLE) clause.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "that", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "clause", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard Stern"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "-- I remember being dragged into this sort of side dungeon and one of your producers saying, OK, this is how this works.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "remember", "being", "dragged", "into", "this", "sort", "of", "side", "dungeon", "and", "one", "of", "your", "producers", "saying", ",", "OK", ",", "this", "is", "how", "this", "works", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry King"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Do you like Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I love Larry King.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Larry", "King", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "I want to have a third show, all right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "have", "a", "third", "show", ",", "all", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Listen, I like you.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "like", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Who's going to buy into that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "going", "to", "buy", "into", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "It was also true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "also", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "But you've never denied being the king of all media?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "'ve", "never", "denied", "being", "the", "king", "of", "all", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "No, I am the king of all media.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "am", "the", "king", "of", "all", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Does that make you the king?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "you", "the", "king", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Who's going to care?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "going", "to", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I want to play you a clip.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "play", "you", "a", "clip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "When is he starting?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "he", "starting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "No one's watching that thing anyway?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "'s", "watching", "that", "thing", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Well, you -- it's not on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "But you don't apologize?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "do", "n't", "apologize", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "No, I want you to be successful.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "want", "you", "to", "be", "successful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What is the secret of being a long-time, successful entertainer in America, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "secret", "of", "being", "a", "long-time", ",", "successful", "entertainer", "in", "America", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I think you have to have a sense of yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "have", "to", "have", "a", "sense", "of", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "If you've got the money that you made, the success you've enjoyed, the status and everything that comes with it, what would motivate you to get out of bed at 3:30, 4:00 every day to carry on doing this?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'ve", "got", "the", "money", "that", "you", "made", ",", "the", "success", "you", "'ve", "enjoyed", ",", "the", "status", "and", "everything", "that", "comes", "with", "it", ",", "what", "would", "motivate", "you", "to", "get", "out", "of", "bed", "at", "3:30", ",", "4:00", "every", "day", "to", "carry", "on", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["3:30"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Do they listen to the show?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "listen", "to", "the", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I think -- my parents listen every day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "my", "parents", "listen", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "And how often does he say to you, \"Great show, Howard\"?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "often", "does", "he", "say", "to", "you", ",", "``", "Great", "show", ",", "Howard", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "``", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Rarely.", "answer_tokens": ["Rarely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Once your dad's called you a genius, you've had all the success and the money, I'm curios as to what makes you, Howard Stern, at 4:00 in the morning, when everyone else is asleep, say, getting out of bed and I'm going to back into battle on the show that often drives me crazy, I'm not even sure I enjoy it?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "your", "dad", "'s", "called", "you", "a", "genius", ",", "you", "'ve", "had", "all", "the", "success", "and", "the", "money", ",", "I", "'m", "curios", "as", "to", "what", "makes", "you", ",", "Howard", "Stern", ",", "at", "4:00", "in", "the", "morning", ",", "when", "everyone", "else", "is", "asleep", ",", "say", ",", "getting", "out", "of", "bed", "and", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "back", "into", "battle", "on", "the", "show", "that", "often", "drives", "me", "crazy", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "even", "sure", "I", "enjoy", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I think it's my identity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "my", "identity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard Stern"], "TIME": ["4:00 in the morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Insecurity?", "question_tokens": ["Insecurity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "TERN: Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["TERN", ":", "Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Are you -- are you sex mad?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "sex", "mad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I'm fascinated by sex.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "fascinated", "by", "sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What did you say to them when you examined them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "to", "them", "when", "you", "examined", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "TERN: I said -- well, I said, they're beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["TERN", ":", "I", "said", "--", "well", ",", "I", "said", ",", "they", "'re", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Then what happens?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "It's nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "They were there with their boyfriends.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "there", "with", "their", "boyfriends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How did the boyfriends feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "the", "boyfriends", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "They seemed to be proud to show --", "answer_tokens": ["They", "seemed", "to", "be", "proud", "to", "show", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "You said yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["You", "said", "yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "The answer was no for me.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "answer", "was", "no", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "You never cheated?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "cheated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "You're always being faithful?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "always", "being", "faithful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I've been faithful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "faithful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Why are you shocked by that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "shocked", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "ORGAN: It's a kind of contradiction.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "It", "'s", "a", "kind", "of", "contradiction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Are you really?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Would you say physically impaired?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "say", "physically", "impaired", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "You want to really get into this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "really", "get", "into", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How many inches are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "inches", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I'm not getting into that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "getting", "into", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Have you ever measured?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "measured", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I'm interviewing you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "interviewing", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Have you ever taken Viagra?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "taken", "Viagra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Never tried it?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "tried", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "No, I don't need it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "need", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Have you ever taken any drug?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "taken", "any", "drug", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Oh, yes, I've had a history with drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "a", "history", "with", "drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Even though you went through that kind of experience?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "though", "you", "went", "through", "that", "kind", "of", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "But for myself, I do not -", "answer_tokens": ["But", "for", "myself", ",", "I", "do", "not", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "As a father, do you actually believe in legalizing drugs as a father?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "father", ",", "do", "you", "actually", "believe", "in", "legalizing", "drugs", "as", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Would you like your kids to have access free to illegal drugs?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "your", "kids", "to", "have", "access", "free", "to", "illegal", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I think that if my -- I think my kids are very strong, they have their heads together.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "if", "my", "--", "I", "think", "my", "kids", "are", "very", "strong", ",", "they", "have", "their", "heads", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beth"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "What are you thoughts when you look at that picture?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thoughts", "when", "you", "look", "at", "that", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Well, Beth is my best friend.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Beth", "is", "my", "best", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Where is your wife?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "your", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "My wife's not here, luckily.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "wife", "'s", "not", "here", ",", "luckily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Are you never about three months down the road?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "never", "about", "three", "months", "down", "the", "road", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "About what?", "question_tokens": ["About", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "This interview is doing pretty well.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "interview", "is", "doing", "pretty", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "How much was your new five-year deal with?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "was", "your", "new", "five-year", "deal", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Well, listen, you know, I've never released financial deals although I read in the paper every day how much I'm worth every day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "released", "financial", "deals", "although", "I", "read", "in", "the", "paper", "every", "day", "how", "much", "I", "'m", "worth", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "You didn't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No, I never took a pay cut.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "took", "a", "pay", "cut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "More or less?", "question_tokens": ["More", "or", "less", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "CC", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "I'm doing -- I'm going to be doing less hours.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "be", "doing", "less", "hours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "More or less than the last deal, as a salary?", "question_tokens": ["More", "or", "less", "than", "the", "last", "deal", ",", "as", "a", "salary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I would say it's about the same.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "it", "'s", "about", "the", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "A little more for a little less work?", "question_tokens": ["A", "little", "more", "for", "a", "little", "less", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "It was a better deal for you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "better", "deal", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "A better deal.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "better", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "When you announced the deal, the stock price went up by 20 percent, presuming you have stock?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "announced", "the", "deal", ",", "the", "stock", "price", "went", "up", "by", "20", "percent", ",", "presuming", "you", "have", "stock", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Well, listen, yes, I do have stock.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "do", "have", "stock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "But who knows?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "knows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Let me show you the first deal, because we can talk about that now.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "show", "you", "the", "first", "deal", ",", "because", "we", "can", "talk", "about", "that", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "So, they were restricting you too much with the fines?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "they", "were", "restricting", "you", "too", "much", "with", "the", "fines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "They were -- they were driving me insane.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "--", "they", "were", "driving", "me", "insane", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "You don't dispute being worth hundreds of millions -- maybe even a billion -- you worth a billion?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "dispute", "being", "worth", "hundreds", "of", "millions", "--", "maybe", "even", "a", "billion", "--", "you", "worth", "a", "billion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you worth a quarter of an Oprah?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "worth", "a", "quarter", "of", "an", "Oprah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Oprah is worth way more money than I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Oprah", "is", "worth", "way", "more", "money", "than", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Does that annoy you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "annoy", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "That the queen of all media is worth more than you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "the", "queen", "of", "all", "media", "is", "worth", "more", "than", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I mean, Oprah -- Oprah was in syndication.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Oprah", "--", "Oprah", "was", "in", "syndication", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan O'Brien"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "What did you think of what he did to Conan O'Brien?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "what", "he", "did", "to", "Conan", "O'Brien", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "And as far -- he did a terrible thing to Conan O'Brien.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "as", "far", "--", "he", "did", "a", "terrible", "thing", "to", "Conan", "O'Brien", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan O'Brien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "I mean, wasn't it just business, really?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "just", "business", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "It -- it's such a -- you ever read Bill Carter's book on it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "--", "it", "'s", "such", "a", "--", "you", "ever", "read", "Bill", "Carter", "'s", "book", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Carter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "-- and someone else comes along?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "someone", "else", "comes", "along", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "But he had made certain guarantees to Conan.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "he", "had", "made", "certain", "guarantees", "to", "Conan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Well, how is it that you're number one in -- in what you do?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "how", "is", "it", "that", "you", "'re", "number", "one", "in", "--", "in", "what", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CD", "IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Letterman"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Who do you most admire in your business?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "most", "admire", "in", "your", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Well, Letterman being one of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Letterman", "being", "one", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "When is this show going off the air?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "this", "show", "going", "off", "the", "air", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Probably the moment this show finishes.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "moment", "this", "show", "finishes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 711, "question": "Is it real -- that hair?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "real", "--", "that", "hair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "The hair is real, and I -- and I --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "hair", "is", "real", ",", "and", "I", "--", "and", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "And you dye it, obviously?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "dye", "it", ",", "obviously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I do not color it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "not", "color", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "-- I have some gray in it.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "have", "some", "gray", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Do you feel -- does it make you feel virile?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "--", "does", "it", "make", "you", "feel", "virile", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I am virile.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "virile", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Are you -- are you romantic?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "romantic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Just ask Howard, is he good in bed?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "ask", "Howard", ",", "is", "he", "good", "in", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Well, you know, I -- that's a tough one.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "--", "that", "'s", "a", "tough", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "How many have said no?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "have", "said", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Well, you know, listen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "listen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "With happiness, or with despair?", "question_tokens": ["With", "happiness", ",", "or", "with", "despair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "I don't know, you watch porno?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "you", "watch", "porno", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Well no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "What's your real view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "real", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "My real view is this, that it -- it's a sad day when I -- I interview many porno stars and I'm fascinated by their lives, because I say, you know, the -- the parents must be like out of their minds.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "real", "view", "is", "this", ",", "that", "it", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "sad", "day", "when", "I", "--", "I", "interview", "many", "porno", "stars", "and", "I", "'m", "fascinated", "by", "their", "lives", ",", "because", "I", "say", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "--", "the", "parents", "must", "be", "like", "out", "of", "their", "minds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "Or do you feel uneasy?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "feel", "uneasy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "First of all, David is a friend of mine.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "David", "is", "a", "friend", "of", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "So as his friend, though, when it backfires, did you feel uneasy about it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "as", "his", "friend", ",", "though", ",", "when", "it", "backfires", ",", "did", "you", "feel", "uneasy", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "I wrote him an e-mail immediately.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wrote", "him", "an", "e-mail", "immediately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 884, "question": "You meant it as a bit of a joke, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "meant", "it", "as", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "joke", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 885, "answer": "Well, a joke -- I started to believe it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "joke", "--", "I", "started", "to", "believe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "Are you -- are you tempted to go again?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "tempted", "to", "go", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 939, "question": "What do you think it's come to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "come", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 940, "answer": "I think America is the greatest country in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "America", "is", "the", "greatest", "country", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1009, "question": "TERN: He left for a personal reason?", "question_tokens": ["TERN", ":", "He", "left", "for", "a", "personal", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1010, "answer": "I'm not going to tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1014, "question": "How big is your penis?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "is", "your", "penis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1015, "answer": "Bigger than yours.", "answer_tokens": ["Bigger", "than", "yours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus"]}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 1022, "question": "And when you see Miley Cyrus, Justin Bieber dominate, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "you", "see", "Miley", "Cyrus", ",", "Justin", "Bieber", "dominate", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1023, "answer": "I love watching these -- like Miley Cyrus grow up and then start taking all her clothes off.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "watching", "these", "--", "like", "Miley", "Cyrus", "grow", "up", "and", "then", "start", "taking", "all", "her", "clothes", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus", "Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1046, "question": "An age thing?", "question_tokens": ["An", "age", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1047, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1049, "question": "Do you worry about getting old?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "getting", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1050, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1055, "question": "Could you imagine being 80 and happy?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "being", "80", "and", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "CD", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1056, "answer": "TERN: I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["TERN", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 1062, "question": "Well what's been -- what's been the moment in your life which, if you had five minutes to live, you would have again?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "what", "'s", "been", "--", "what", "'s", "been", "the", "moment", "in", "your", "life", "which", ",", "if", "you", "had", "five", "minutes", "to", "live", ",", "you", "would", "have", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1063, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1084, "question": "Did he ever tell you that he loves you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "tell", "you", "that", "he", "loves", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1085, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1102, "question": "In the end, you are just a shameless little plugger, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "end", ",", "you", "are", "just", "a", "shameless", "little", "plugger", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1103, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]